SARAH JOHNSON

Health care account manager with 15+years of experience working for hospitals to streamline patient experiences and insurance negotiations. Comprehensive knowledge of the health care industry and great communication and presentation skills that led to S10M in additional revenue. Expert user of EHR systems and medical billingand coding.

123 First Street, Seattle, WA12345 youremai I @emai I, coin (123)456-7890

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

ACCOUNT MANAGER

General Uptown Hospital, Seattle, WA August2010-Present

ASSOCIATE ACCOUNT

REPRESENTATIVE

Home Healthcare, Co., Baltimore, MD September 2006 - May 2010

- Resolve questions and billing errors for more than 75+ patients daily
- ♦ Collaborated with various teams to develop effective marketing that led to an increase in patient numbers of 4.2%
- Manage all corporate communications to ensure brand integrity, including internal and external documents
- Worked with health care providers to create improved patient scheduling practices that resulted in increased customer satisfaction and reduced wait times by 26%
- Created a referral network with local primary care doctors that generated \$3M in new revenue
- Designed and implemented new marketing strategies to better educate consumers on available services

EDUCATION

Master of Business Administration

Johns Hopkins University, Baltimore, MD August 2008 - June 2010 3.79 GPA

Bachelor of Healthcare Administration

Seattle University, Seattle, WA, August 2002 - June 2006 3.86 GPA

KEY SKILLS

- Budget building
- ♦ EHR
- ♦ HR
- ♦ Leadership
- Marketing design and strategy
- ♦ Medical billing and coding
- Organized with excellent attention to detail
- Strongcommunicator

CERTIFICATIONS

- AAPC C e rti fied Professiona I Coder, 2005
- Certified Professional in Healthcare Information and Management Systems, 2007